HANNAH EWING

1023 South Pike Avenue Bolivar, Missouri 65613 (417) 955-0766 hewing777@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Sciences in Accounting & Information Assurance

Southwest Baptist University Graduation: May 2021

GPA: 3.48

Bachelor of Sciences in Cyber Security

Southwest Baptist University Graduation: May 2021

GPA: 3.48

PERSONAL INFORMATION & INTERESTS

I am currently a full time student at Southwest Baptist University. In my spare time I enjoy reading, running, traveling and volunteering at my church.

SKILLS

- Communication
- Java Programming Language, C+ Programming Language, Excel, Microsoft Word, and PowerPoint
- Clerical
- Critical Thinking
- Organization
- Time Management

SUMMARY

I will graduate in May of 2021. Upon graduation I will have four years experience working as an intern in the accounting department at Citizens Memorial Hospital. After graduation I would like to pursue a career in either cyber security or forensic accounting.

EXPERIENCE

Accounting Intern

Citizens Memorial Hospital April 2017 - Present

- -Data Entry
- -Balanced Accounts
- -Made Journal Entries

Alumni Relations

Southwest Baptist University August 2016 to April 2017

- -Data Entry
- -Filled Mail
- -Made Calls

Cashier

Lucas Oil Speedway April 2014 to October 2016

- -Made Change
- -Interacted with Customers
- -Balanced my Drawer